dating.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy policy

## Privacy Policy

Date last revised: September 28, 2012

Dating.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. Because we operate from offices around the world, we have taken steps to ensure that high standards of data protection are adhered to globally. This statement outlines our privacy and data protection policy.

#### Acceptance of Privacy Policy

Each time you access, use, post, submit a post or reply, or browse Dating.com (or any of its subdomains), hereafter referred to as Dating.com, you signify your acceptance of our then-current Privacy Policy. If you do not accept this Privacy Policy, you are not authorized to use Dating.com and must discontinue use of Dating.com immediately.

#### Collection of Non-Personal Information Using Cookies

Please see Cookie policy.

#### Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect personal information about you whenever you engage in transactions on Dating.com, create or update account information, or communicate with us. The personal information we collect and store about you may include without limitation your first and last name, email address, credit or debit card number, billing and shipping information, order history, and other non-public information about you.

We may use the information we collect to:

  * manage your registration preferences
  * send you renewal notifications and/or service notifications, contact you regarding your posts, replies, and/or account information;
  * personalize web content and advertising based on your personal characteristics or preferences, using this to enhance Dating.com
  * ensure, as far as is practical, that our websites and applications are compatible with the browsers and operating systems used by most of our visitors
  * conduct customer satisfaction surveys

We may also:

  * tell you about additional products and services
  * invite you to participate in market research and surveys
  * use your information for in-house research and analysis. This helps us to: 
    * improve our understanding of customer needs
    * create marketing profiles
    * support strategic development

You authorize Dating.com to transmit email to you to respond to your communications and administer Activities.

#### Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

During the course of normal business, Dating.com **does not disclose** your personal information to any third parties.

#### Disclosure In Unusual Circumstances

We may disclose also your name, email address, or other information about you, including personal information, **if** (i) required to do so by law, court order or subpoena, or as requested by other government, law enforcement, or investigative authority, (ii) if we determine an ad posted violates our Terms of Use, or (iii) there is an emergency involving personal danger.

Please note that if you post any of your personal information on Dating.com, such information may be collected and used by others over whom Dating.com has no control. Dating.com is not responsible for the use by third parties of information you post or otherwise make public.

#### Children under 13

Dating.com does not intentionally collect any personal information from individuals under the age of 13. When necessary, underage users will be told not to submit any personal details and we will make every effort to delete any details of such users where a parent or guardian has informed us that these details have been collected.

Note: Dating.com is an adult oriented site, and has been voluntarily registered with the following parental control programs to keep your children safe from adult materials: Net Nanny, Cyber Patrol, Cyber Sitter, Safe Surf, FOSI. We do not collect information from any person not of legal age, and the use of the site by persons not of legal age is a violation of the [Terms of Use of Dating.com](http://dating.com/http/tos).

#### Communication from Dating.com

From time to time, Dating.com may send you information with announcements and updates about Dating.com and your account. You may elect to opt out of ongoing e-mail communication from us, such as newsletters, account information, promotional materials, etc. by using a simple opt-out procedure. You need only click on the bottom Unsubscribe link in the email, and you will be removed from the relevant mailing list.

#### Correction/Update of Personal Information

If your personal information changes, you may review/correct/update your personal information previously provided at any time by updating your information in the my account section of Dating.com. If you wish your personal data to be deleted from Dating.com, you may email us at support@dating.com and we will do so. Note that requesting we delete your personal data from Dating.com will result in the de-activation of your account and subsequent loss of access to Dating.com.

#### Links to Other sites

Dating.com provides links and pointers to websites maintained by other organizations. Dating.com provides these links as a convenience to users, but it does not operate, control or endorse such sites. Dating.com also disclaims any responsibility for the information on those sites and any products or services offered there, and cannot vouch for the privacy policies of such sites. Dating.com does not make any warranties or representations that any linked sites (or even this Site) will function without error or interruption, that defects will be corrected, or that Dating.com and their servers are free of viruses and other problems that can harm your computer.

#### Security Policy

Dating.com does its utmost to protect your privacy and ensure your personal details are not misused, accidentally destroyed, lost or altered within Dating.com. We use best practices in the design of our technical infrastructure to ensure the safety and secure of your personal data with us.

Due to the nature of the Internet and our reliance on third party vendors, we absolutely cannot guarantee Dating.com’s uptime or the security of your data.

#### Policy Changes and Acceptance

The Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time as we add new features and services, as laws change, and as industry privacy and security best practices evolve. We display an effective date on the upper left corner of the Privacy Policy so that it will be easier for you to know when there has been a change. Accordingly, you should check the Privacy Policy on a regular basis for the most current privacy practices. Each time you access, use or browse Dating.com, you signify your acceptance of the then-current changes to the Privacy Policy applying to your personal information collected by us on and from the effective date of such changes.

Any changes in the Privacy Policy will take effect upon posting and apply only to information collected from you on and after Last Revised date, unless we provide notice or have other communications with you.

#### Additional Questions?

If you have any questions or queries about this Privacy Policy, e-mail them to support@dating.com.
